Guide to the John Wesley Hardin Papers
The Wittliff Collections
Letters From: 1893 Jun 30 Howell, Frank – Friend of R.R. Coleman Letters From: 1894 Oct 21 Hudson, R.B. – Sheriff of Dewitt Co. Letters From: 1894 Nov 1
Jernigan, Lomax - Purity Bowen writes from Florida that Lomax killed relation Steve Jones in a drunken fight in Pollard. Several Jernigans married into the Bowen family (Parsons, Brown 138) Mentioned: 1881 May 1
Jones, B. H.-Probably cousin Barnett Jones who was with Hardin in the John Gates saloon when Hardin was shot by Phil Sublett in 1872. Mentioned: 1879, Jul 6
Jones, Caroline-Rents cottage to Hardin as Swain in Jacksonville. Letters From: 1876 Apr 27
Jones, Lizzie - Purity Bowen mentions death in letter from Florida. Mentioned: 1881 May 1
Jones, Steve (Steave) - Purity Bowen in letter from Florida mentions Jone's killing in a drunken fight in Pollard, Alabama. Mentioned: 1881 May 1
Jones, Willis-Purity Bown calls him uncle and mentions death in letter from Florida. Mentioned: 1881 May 1
Jones, W.E. – Sheriff of Gonzales Co. Letters From – 1894 Nov 3
Karnes, Sheriff John-see Carnes
Kelso, Frank – Friend of R.R. Coleman Letters From: 1894 Oct 20 Kendrick, M. E.-Jacksonville Florida buyer of beef from Hardin as J. H. Swain. Letters From: 1876, Jan 26[?],
Kimbro, Manen-Mannen Clements writes Jane that Kimbro brought him news of her family. Mentioned: 1879 Mar 23
King, Fannie - friend of Jane Hardin
Krueger, O.P. – Friend of J.W. Hardin Letters From: 1894 Nov 20 Kotzel, - Druggist Letters To: 1894 Oct 29
Landrum, J. C.-teacher of Hardin and brother Joseph. Mentioned: 1878 Jun 27
La Opinion Del Pueblo – Gonzales paper –
Letters From: 1894 Oct 13 – Vol 1 No 2 Lay, John - Friend to J.W. Hardin
Letter From: 1894 May 20, Jun 22. Levyson, P. - General store owner - Gonzales. Letters From: 1894 May 23 (bill) Lewis, Callie – see Jennie Hardin Letters From: 1894 Dec 30 Lewis, Judge-Judge who heard Mannen Clements trial for the killing of Peyton Patterson in Gonzales County during February of 1878. Mentioned: 1878 Jan 31
Lipscomb, J A.-Attorney hired by Robert Hardin to defend Hardin Letters From: 1877 undated Mentioned: 1877 Oct 29
Loide-Mentioned in letter by mother of Bright Smith, Hardin's brother-in-law. Mentioned: 1882 May 1
Long, J.D.- friend of J.W. Hardin. Letters From: 1894 Mar 8
Mann, Jim-friend. Was with Hardin when he was overpowered on the train in Pensacola. Mann was shot and killed as he tried to run off the train. Mentioned: 1877, Aug 25
Mat-mentioned in 1882 letter from Mattie Odom, living with her in 1883. Mentioned: 1882 Oct 4; 1883 Feb 16
Mendoza, M. – Wife of Roman Augurero Letters To: 1894 Oct 7 McCall, J.D. – Comptroller Letters From: 1894 Jan 9 McCulloch, Capt. Ben-Superintendent at the Texas Prison System. Letters To: 1885 Aug 26 Mentioned: 1888 Jan 22
McGee, Duncan-friend or relative of the Bowens. Mentioned: 1877, Dec 20
McKenzie, J. W. T.-friend of Hardin family. Mentioned: 1877 Oct 26.
McKinney, A.T. – Prison warden(?) Letters To: 1893 Jul 14 McMillan, Marion (A. M.)-Jane's cousin, a probate judge in Pollard, Alabama Letters From: 1877 Sep 16 Letter To: 1877, Aug 25 Mentioned: 1877, May 6
McMillan, Mary-probably wife of Malcolm McMillan and relation to Jane Bowen. Mentioned in Purity's letter from Florida. Mentioned: 1881 May 1
McMillan, Neill-Jane Bowen's relative. Deputy sheriff of Pollard, Alabama with whom the Hardins stayed under the name of Swain. Mentioned: 1877, Jun 6, Dec 5, 20
McQueen-friend of Jane Hardin. Mentioned: 1877, May 9
Moody, Dr. - Doctor in Red River County. Mentioned: 1879 Apr 27
Morgan, J. B.-Killed by Hardin in Cuero in 1872. Mentioned: 1878 Jun 11
Newman (Numan), Sunny (Sonny)-friend of Bowens. Mentioned: 1877 Dec 5, 20
Nixon, H. A. - Gonzales Attorney. Letter From: 1890 Mar 7
Odom, Frankey (Frank)-Mattie Bowen Odom's son, born May 1880. (Parsons, Bowen 140) Mentioned: 1881 Mar 5, Apr 26, Dec 14; 1882 Jan 18, May 28; 1883 Feb 16
Odom, Mattie Bowen - (see also Mattie Bowen)-sister-in-law. Married Oliver Odom December 1878. Letters From: 1879 Mar 16, May 13, Jun 15, Jul 22; 1881 Mar 5, Apr 26, Dec 14; 1882 Jan 18, May 28, Oct 4; 1883 Feb 16 Mentioned: 1879, Mar 23; 1881 Aug 14
Odom, Oliver-married Jane's sister Mattie Bowen. Is on trial in 1881 according to Mattie's letters. Parsons reports he was indicted in 1878 for an 1874 murder. He died June 22, 1881. (Parsons, Bowen 140) Letter From: 1879 May 13 Mentioned: 1879 Feb 9, Mar 23, Jun 15, Jul 22; 1881 Mar 5, Apr 26
Outlaw, J. C.-guard through whom Hardin was able to slip out letters. Mentioned: 1878 Dec 3, 8, 23, 28
Passmore, Ben-Bowen relation mentioned in letter from Joshua Bowen to Edward B. Bowen. Mentioned: 1880 Jul 15,
Patterson, Paten (Peyton, Pate)-Mannen Clements was indicted October 17, 1877 for the killing of Patterson on July 25, 1872. Clements was arrested December 19, 1877 and won acquittal in 1878. Mentioned: 1878 Jan 29, Mar 17, May 30
Phillips, Bill (William) - husband of Nancy Bowen, Jane Hardin's sister. Mentioned: 1878 May 2?, Jun 29, Jul 14, Oct 21, 22/27; 1879 Feb 9, Mar 7, May 13[?]
Phillips, Nancy Bowen -sister-in-law, married to William Phillips. Mentioned: 1877 Sep 5, Oct 26, 1878 Jul 14, May 13; 1881 Apr 26; 1882 Apr 2; 1888 May 22
Powell,[?] Houston-acquaintance, prison inmate. Mentioned: 1879 May 4,
Randle, J.P. - General store owner in Gonzales Letters To: 1894 - bill - May 9. Aug 4 Rauckedt - cousin to Mattie Odem
Renick, S. H.-attorney in Waco. Defends Hardin in Webb trial and appeal. Letters From: 1878 Apr 16 Mentioned: 1878 Mar 17, Apr 6, 19
Reynolds, Lieutenant-guarded Hardin on his way to Comanche for sentencing and on his way to Huntsville. Mentioned: 1878 Oct 4
Ringo, John - incarcerated in Austin jail at the same time as Hardin. Mentioned: 1879 Apr 13, Jul 6
Reuter, Charles - owner Gonzales Ice Works. Letters From: 1894 Sept 1 (bill)
S., John-fellow inmate. Debates with Hardin in the Debating Society defending the premise that women should have equal rights. Mentioned: 1881 Jul 3
S., J. [John] G. [?], friend living in Thomasville, Georgia. Identity unknown. Letters To: 1876, Sep 8
Sallie-possibly Jane's niece, Frank's daughter. Mentioned: 1882 May 28
Schlikeisen, E.F. - Sold J.W. Hardin a horse. Letters From: 1894 Aug 10 (bill) Scott, J. B.-may be same as below. Promises to be at Hardin's appeal. Mentioned: 1878 May 2[?]
Scott, Mr. of Marlin-Mattie Hardin mentions him. Possibly lawyer hired by Mr. Choat of Karnes County to represent Hardin in his appeal. Mentioned: 1877 Nov 26
Shegog, Dr. J. M. - Uncle, married to Elizabeth Hardin's sister, Nan. Lives in Ennis, Ellis County. Mentioned: 1878 Apr 7; 1885 May 29; 1886 Aug 3
Shegog, Nan-Aunt, Elizabeth Hardin's sister living in Ennis. Mentioned: 1877 May 9, Oct 10; 1878, Feb 17, Dec 3, 8; 1879 Sep 21; 1885 May 29; 1886 Aug 3; 1888 Feb 5
Shepard, Seth-lawyer. Robert Hardin tried to hire for Hardin's Comanche County trial Mentioned: 1877, Sep 9
Shroeder, Molly-Jennie Hardin's teacher. Mentioned: 1887 Aug 28
Smith, Dick-Mentioned in letter from Bright Smith's mother. Mentioned: 1882 May 1
Smith, Bright-brother-in-law. Married Hardin's sister, Mattie. Letters To: 1879 Mar 16 Mentioned: 1877, May 9, Sep 9, 15, Oct 26-27, Nov 21, 25, Dec 5, 29; 1878 Feb 26, May 30, Jun 15, 23, 27, Jul 4, 14, Oct 4, Oct 10, 20; 1879 Mar 2, Apr 27, Jul 30, Sep 21; 1880 Apr 24, May 27; 1882 Feb 26, May 1, May 25, Aug 13; 1886 Jan 3, Aug 3, Smith, L. J. - friend of Hardin's from Jacksonville, Florida. Mentioned: 1878 Jun 23
Smith, Lillie-niece, first child of sister Mattie Smith born in 1878 Mentioned: 1878 Mar 11, Jun 15, Oct 10; 1879 Mar 2; 1880 Apr 24; 1886 Aug 3
Smith, M. A.-Probably Bright Smith's mother. Bright is married to Hardin's sister, Mattie. Letter From: 1882 May 1; 1886 Aug 3
Smith, Mattie Hardin-sister. Married Bright Smith in 1876. Letters To: 1879 Feb 23 (note), Mar 16; Letters From: 1877 Sep 15, Nov 21, 25, Dec 29; 1886 Aug 3; 1893 Oct 17 Mentioned: 1877, May 9, Sep 9, 12, Oct 14, 26-27, Nov 21, Dec 5; 1878 Feb 15, 26, Mar 11, Mar 17, Jun 8, 15, 23, Jul 4, 9, 14, Aug 16, 30, 31, Oct 10, 20, Dec 8 1879 Mar 2, Jul 30, Sep 21; 1880 Apr 24; 1882 Feb 2, May 25, Aug 13; 1885 Nov 22; 1886 Jan 3
Smith, J.F - County clerk- Brown Co. Letters from: 1893 May 29 Smither, Capt. J. G..-prison assistant superintendent. Letters To: 1889 [?]; 1893 Oct 29, Nov ?; 1894 Feb 7 Mentioned: 1890 Apr 6; 1891 Aug 4
Steadman, Ed-Prison inmate who had helped John Ringo and George Cooley break out of the Lampasas County jail. Mentioned: 1879 Apr 13
Stephens, J. D. (Stevens)-Prosecuting attorney at Hardin's Comanche County trial. Mentioned: 1877 Oct 26, undated, Dec 5
Steward, Joe-Acquaintance in Austin. Mentioned: 1878 Aug 28; 1879 Apr 13
Sunday, Joe-brother to Neill Bowen's second wife, Purity. (Parsons, 46) Mentioned: 1878, May 2?, Aug 2
Sutton faction- Mentioned: 1877 May 6; 1878 Jun 15; 1879 Apr 13
Swain, Jane-see Jane Bowen Hardin. Letters To: 1877 May 6, 9, Jun 6, Aug 25
Swain, Jennie-Acquaintance of the Hardins in Brenham. Mentioned: 1877 May 9, Sep 12
Swain, J. H.-see John Wesley Hardin. Takes alias after he flees Texas in late 1874. He adopts the last name of the Brenham marshal, Harry Swain, who helped Hardin get out of Texas. Letter From: 1876- May 12; 1877 (Millview, Florida) Jun 6, Aug 25 Letter To: 1875, Sep 25; 1876, Jan 24, 26, Mar 23, Apr 27, May 1, May 2, 12; 1877 May 9, Jun 6, Aug 25
Talmadge, Rev. T. De Witt-syndicated columnist. Hardin is inspired by his teaching and sends clipping to Jane. Mentioned: 1888 Mar 25 (with clippings)
Taylor, Billy-son of Pitkin Taylor who was killed by the Sutton faction in 1872. With the help of Hardin, Billy along with his brother attacked Bill Sutton on a steamer in Indianola, Texas on March 11, 1874. Billy Taylor killed Sutton's companion, Gabriel Slaughter. In 1877, Taylor was in an Austin jail for this killing at the same time as Hardin. Mentioned: 1877 May 6, May 9; 1878 Jan 29, Jun 15, 27
Taylor, James- Son of Pitkin Taylor born 1852 and a leader in the Sutton-Taylor feud. Along with Hardin, killed Jack Helm July 1873. With the help of Hardin, along with brother Billy Taylor, killed Bill Sutton on a steamer in Indianola, March 11, 1874. Taylor himself was killed by a Sutton posse in Clinton, Texas on December 27, 1875. Mentioned: 1877 May 6, May 9, Oct 29
Taylor, J.M. - Friend of J.W. Hardin.
Letter from: 1894 Apr, 28. Oct 31 Taylor, Scrap-Lynched after Webb killing. Mentioned: 1879 May 11
Templeton, Bill-prison inmate. Mentioned: 1879 Apr 13
Tennille, Mrs. [Amanda Jane Billings] Mentioned: 1877, May 6
Tennille, Tony-married Nannie Cobb. Mentioned: 1877, May 6, Sept 5
TEXAS, STATE OF Letters To: 1893 Oct 17 (Cooke Co.); 1894 Aug 10 (Gonzales Co.), Oct 27 (Gonzales Co.), Oct 31 (Gonzales Co.), Nov 1 (Gonzales Co.), Dec 16 (DeWitt Co. – Hardin/Billings marriage certificate) Tom-Hardin writes Jane to tell Mannen that Tom is all right. Mentioned: 1878 Oct 4
Turner, Mr.-J. H. Clements thanks for "kindness and indulgence" to Mannen Clements during his Austin incarceration. Mentioned: 1878 Jan 31
Turner, Sara -Cousin Mentioned: 1879 July 30
Tyler, Marcus-Oliver Odom reports to Mannen Clements that Tyler has several indictments against him. Mentioned: 1879 May 13
Unknown Letter From: 1876 Jan 24
Vancleaves, Mat - Jane's sister Matt and her husband Oliver Odom live with the Vancleaves in 1879.
Vandegriff, Major-Ranger wrote Hardin from Austin that Jane had started for his mother's home in October 1878. Mentioned: 1878 Oct 10, 21
Wad-Has been identified as Wes but the text of the letter indicates it is more likely written to a person living and working in the free world. The 1880 Gonzales County Census lists a Wadkin Ellis, a 45 year old farmer, living near the Bowens. Letter To: 1882 Nov 26
Waller, Bill-Ranger that hunted Hardin after the Webb killing. Mentioned: 1878 Oct 20
Webb, Charles-Deputy Sheriff of Brown County killed by Hardin on April 1874. Hardin received a sentence for 25 years in the penitentiary for the killing. Mentioned: 1877 Oct 26, 29, Nov 21, undated, Dec 5; 1888 Jun 24; 1889 Jul 14
West, M.L. – Bondsman in Floresville, TX. Letters From: 1894 Oct 15 Whattley, D.A. Superintendent of State Penitentiaries, Huntsville. Letters From: 1891 Aug 4; White, Mr. - mentioned in letter from Mattie Odom in 1882. He might move out west Mentioned: 1882 Oct 4
Willard, E. E.-City Clerk in Jacksonville Florida who records Hardin's (alias Swain) payments on a stall in the meat market. Letters From: 1876, May 1 (2)
Wilson, Frank-Deputy sheriff of Comanche County present at Webb killing. Mentioned: 1877, Sep 9; 1878 Oct 4, Oct 27
Wingate, J.F. – Prison mate of J.W. Hardin Letters From: 1894 Oct 21
Wright family - Friends of Jane's. Mattie Odom tells Jane to say hello Mentioned: 1881 Dec 14; 1882 Jan 18, Feb 26
Outlaws; Frontier and pioneer life -- Texas; Correspondence; Hardin, John Wesley, 1853-1895
- Correspondence, 1874-1895, undated
  - 1874-1877 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Sept 8, 1874. J.W. Hardin to J.G. Hardin
    Sept 25, 1875. Joseph DeMartini to J.H. Swain
    Jan 24, 1876. [Unknown] to J.H. Swain
    Jan 2[6], 1876. M.E. Kendrick to J.H. Swain
    Mar 23, 1876. L.M. Downing to J.H. Swain
    Apr 27, 1876. C. Jones to J.H. Swain
    May 1, 1876. E.E. Willard to J.H. Swain
    May 1, 1876. E.E. Willard to L.M. Downing
    May 2, 1876. B.R. Dinkins to J.H. Swain
    May 12, 1876. J.H. Swain to Mr. Benham
    May 12, 1876. [Unknown] to J.H. Swain
    Sep 8, 1876. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 6, 1877. Joshua Bowden to Jane Swain
    May 9, 1877. R.E. Barnette to J.H. Swain
    Jun 6, 1877. J.H. Swain to Jane Swain
    Aug 25, 1877. J.H. Swain to Jane Swain
    Sep 5, 1877. Mattie Bowen to Jane Hardin
    Sept 8, 18[77]. J.W. Hardin to [Friend] [Photocopy]
    Sept 9, 1877. Mattie Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Sept 9, 1877. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Sept 9, 1877. Alie B. Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Sept 9, 1877. Mattie Hardin to J.W. Hardin [Missing]
    Sept 12, 1877. Mattie Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 15, 1877. Mattie Smith to J.W. Hardin
    Sept 16, 1877. Marion McMillan to Jane Swain[unknown] Lizzie Cobb to J.W. Hardin
    Oct 13, 1877. Doc J. An to J.W. Hardin
    Oct 14, 1877. Mattie Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 26, 1877. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Oct 26, 1877. William Bowen to Jane Hardin [Missing w/note]
    Oct 26, 1877. Mattie Bowen to Jane Hardin
    Oct 27, 18[77]. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Oct 29, 1877. Mattie Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    [unknown] A.J. Lipscomb to J.W. Hardin
    Nov 21, 1877. Mattie Smith to J.W. Hardin
    Nov 25, 1877. Mattie Smith to Jane Hardin
    [unknown] Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Nov 26, 1877. Mattie Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Dec 3, 1877. A.C. Dikes to J.W. Hardin
    Dec 5, 1877. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 14, 1877. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 20, 1877. Mattie Bowen to Jane Hardin
    Dec 29, 1877. Mattie Smith to Jane Hardin
    [unknown] R.E. Barnette to Jane Hardin
  - 1878 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Jan 15, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Jan 29, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jan 31, 1878. J.H. Clements to J.W. Hardin
    Feb 15, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Feb 15, 1878. J.H. Clements to J.W. Hardin
    Feb 17, 1878. Lizzie Cobb to J.W. Hardin
    Feb 26, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Mar 11, 1878. Lizzie Cobb to J.W. Hardin
    Mar 14, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 17, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 9, 1878. Mary C. Campbell to Jane Hardin
    Mar 15, 1878. John C. Godfrey & W. B. Hardin to J.W. Hardin [Verso] Mar 26, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & Mother, Sisters & Brothers
    Mar 30, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Apr 6, 1878. W.B. Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Apr 7, 1878. John C. Godfrey to J.W. Hardin
    Apr 16, 1878. S.H. Renick to J.W. Hardin
    Apr 19, 1878. Mattie Bowen to Jane Hardin
    Apr 29, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 18, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 2[1], 1878. Mannen Clements to J.W. Hardin
    May 30, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Jun 1, 1878. Mannen Clements to Jane Hardin
    Jun 2, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jun 7, 1878. Molly E. Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Jun 8, 1878. Nannie Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Jun 11, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jun 15, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jun 23, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jun 27, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jun 29, 1878. Mattie Bowen to Jane Hardin
    Jul 4, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jul 9, 1878. Nannie Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Jul 14, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Aug 2, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Aug 3, 1878. Mannen Clements to Jane Hardin
    [unknown] S.E.H. to Jane Hardin
    Aug 16, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Aug 19, 1878. Mattie Bowen to Jane Hardin
    Aug 27, 1878. Mannen Clements to Jane Hardin
    Aug 28, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Aug 30, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to J.W. & Jane Hardin
    Aug 31, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 11, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 16, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 17, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 24, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 4, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 10, 1878. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 20, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    [Oct 20, 1878]. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 21, 1878. Mannen Clements to Jane Hardin
    [Oct 22] 1878. John S. Vandegriff to J.W. Hardin [Verso] Oct 27, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Nov 17, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 3, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 8, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & Elizabeth Hardin
    Dec 23, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 28, 1878. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
  - 1879 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Jan 9, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jan 10, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jan 26, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Feb 9, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Feb 23, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 2, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 16, 1879. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Mar 16, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Mattie Smith & Jane Hardin
    Mar 23, 1879. Mary A. Clements to Jane Hardin
    Apr 13, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Apr 20, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Apr 27, 1879. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 4, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 11, 1879. J.W. Hardin to M. Clements & Jane Hardin
    May 13, 1879. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    May 13, 1879. Oliver Odom to Jane Hardin
    May 25, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & M. Clements
    Jun 1, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jun 15, 1879. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Jun 19, 1879. S.J. Clements to Jane Hardin
    Jul 2, 1879. M.J. Cobb to Jane Hardin
    Jul 6, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & M. Clements
    Jul 22, 1879. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Jul 27, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & M. Clements
    Jul 30, 1879. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Aug 10, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & M. Clements
    Aug 17, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & [Cousin]
    Sept 21, 1879. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 21, 1879. Nannie Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 21, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin & Mollie and Cousin
    Nov 2, 1879. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
  - 1880-1888 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Apr 24, 1880. Nannie Hardin to Mollie Hardin
    May 27, 1880. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jul 13, 1880. Edward Bowen to copy book
    July 15, 1880. Joshua Bowen to Edward Bowen
    Aug 30, 1880. Elizabeth Hadin to Jane Hardin
    March 5, 1881. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Apr 26, 1881. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    May 1, 1881. Purity Bowen to Jane Hardin
    June 3, 1881. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jul 3, 1881. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Aug 14, 1881. J.W Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 25, 1881. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 14, 1881. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Jan 18, 1882. Mattie to Jane Hardin
    Feb 26, 1882. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    [Feb-Mar] 1882. Professor Peace and Scholars to [Unknown]
    Apr 2, 1882. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May [1] 1882. M.A. Smith to [Daughter]
    May [28] 1882. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Aug 13, 1882. Elizabeth Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Sept 3, 1882. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 1, 1882. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 1, 1882. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin [Missing]
    Oct 4, 1882. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin & Mollie Hardin
    Nov 26, 1882. Neill Bowen to Wad
    Feb 16, 1883. Mattie Odom to Jane Hardin
    Jan 6, 1884. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 7, 1884. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 29, 1885. J.M. Shegog, RE: Elizabeth Hardin's funeral
    Aug 26, 1885. J.W. Hardin to B. McCulloch
    Sept 27, 1885. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Nov 22, 1885. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jan 3, 1886. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 7, 1886. J.W. Hardin to J. Hardin, Jr.
    May 2, 1886. J.W. Hardin to Jennie Hardin
    Aug 3, 1886. Mattie Smith to Jane Hardin
    Sept 5, 1886. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 3, 1886. J.W. Hardin to Mollie Hardin
    Nov 7, 1886. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 27, 1887. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Apr 3, 1887. J.W. Hardin to J. Hardin, Jr.
    May 1, 1887. J.W. Hardin to Jennie Hardin
    Aug 28, 1887. J.W. Hardin to Jennie Hardin
    Sept 4, 1887. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Nov 6, 1887. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jan 22, 1888. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Feb 5, 1888. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Mar 25, 1888. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    May 22, 1888. [F.M. Bond] to Jane Hardin
    June 24, 1888. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Oct 7, 1888. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Dec 25, 1888. Prison Playbill
  - 1889-1893 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Jan 8 [1889]. J.W. Hardin to Molly Hardin
    Jan 22 [1889]. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    [unknown] J.W. Hardin to Captain Smithers
    Feb 1, 1889. J.W. Hardin to Texas Legislature
    Apr 15, 1889. C. Eckhardt & Sons to Jane Hardin
    May 5, 1889. J.W. Hardin to Molly Hardin
    July 14, 1889. J.W. Hardin to Jennie Hardin
    Oct 20, 1889. J.W. Hardin to J. Hardin, Jr.
    Dec 8, 1889. J.W. Hardin to Jennie Hardin
    Mar 7, 1890. H.A. Nixon to J.E. Hooper
    Apr 6, 1890. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Nov 2, 1890. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Apr 5, 1891. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Aug 4, 1891. D.A. Whattley to J.W. Hardin
    Oct 25, 1891. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    [Sept] 11, [1891]. [J.W. Hardin] to Mollie Hardin
    [unknown] Mattie Odem to [Mr.] Rauckedt
    [unknown] Fannie King to Jane Hardin
    [unknown] Mollie Anglin to Jane Hardin
    [unknown] [Jas] Hardin to J.W. Hardin
    Jan 4, 1892. J.W. Hardin to Jane Hardin
    Jan 8, 1892. Fly & McNeal to J.W. Hardin
    [unknown] Citizens of Gonzales to Gov. J.S. Hogg
    [Jan 25, 1891]. Fly & McNeal to J.W. Hardin
    May 18, 1892. Fly & McNeal to J.W. Hardin
    Jul 17, 1892. James Anderson to J.W. Hardin
    Aug 21, 1892. J.W. Hardin to Molly Hardin
    Aug 28, 1892. J.W. Hardin to J. Hardin, Jr.
    Aug 30, 1892. J.W. Hardin to [Unknown] [Missing]
    Sept 11, 1892. J.W. Hardin to J.B. Cobb
    Oct 24, 1892. [Unknown] to W.J. Gary
    Nov 6, 1892. J.W. Hardin to J.B. Cobb
    Nov 28, 1892. Notice of death for Jane Hardin
    May 18, 1893. [Unknown] to J.B. Cobb [Missing]
    [unknown, 1893] [J.W. Hardin] to J. Smither
    May 29, 1893. J.F. Smith to [Unknown]
    Jun 29, 1893. E. Howell to Mollie Hardin & Jennie Hardin
    Jul 14, 1893. K.R. Blackshear to J.W. Hardin
    Jul 14, 1893. K.R. Blackshear to A.T. McKinney
    Oct 17, 1893. Mattie Smith to State of Texas [Attached] Oct 17, 1893. J.W. Hardin to State of Texas
    Oct 29, 1893. J.W. Hardin to Governor J.S. Hogg [Attached] Dec 24, 1891. [County Clerk] to State of Texas